[
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p2",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_01",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_22||(99_MSQ_23&&!99_MSQ_35)",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p2",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_02",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT3",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p5",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_02",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT3_Handwear_30",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_complete_available_response_multi",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_alt",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p5",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_02",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_alt_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT3_Handwear_30",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_complete_available_response_multi",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p4",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_04",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_03",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT3_Footwear_30",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_05_findingfort",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 31,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p4",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_05",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_04",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT3",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p4",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_06",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_05",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionFamilyWardLostT5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 3,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Sun_p2",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_07",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_06",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "HoningStoneT3",
		"ItemRewardQty": 3,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_08_azothtree",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p6",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_07",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT3",
		"ItemRewardQty": 10,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 33,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p6",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_08 && !Archetype_Mercenary && !Archetype_Warmonger && !Archetype_Tracker && !Archetype_Musketeer && !Archetype_Occultist && !Archetype_Theurgist && !Archetype_Wanderer",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_destroyer",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 33,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p6",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Warmonger",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_success_destroyer",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_musketeer",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 33,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p6",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Musketeer",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_success_musketeer",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_mystic",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 33,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p6",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Theurgist",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_success_mystic",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_occultist",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 33,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p6",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Occultist",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_success_occultist",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_ranger",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 33,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p6",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Tracker",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_success_ranger",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_soldier",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 33,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p6",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Mercenary",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_success_soldier",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_QuestReward_ArcTyp_BW_1hRshield",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_swordsman",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 33,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p6",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Wanderer",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_success_swordsman",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 34,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p9",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_10",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_09",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "QuestReward_MSQ2_2hFishingPole_Yonas",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2",
		"NOTE": "Soul Trial"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_alt",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 34,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p9",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_10",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_09",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_alt_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "QuestReward_MSQ2_2hFishingPole_Yonas",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2",
		"NOTE": "Soul Trial alt"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 34,
		"Task": "99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p8",
		"AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_11",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_10",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "ringbrightwoodt4",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	}
]